<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Play</title>
	<atom:link href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz</link>
	<description>by Metrica Sports</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 15:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/favicon-150x128.png</url>
	<title>Play</title>
	<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Welcome aboard, Levante UD</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/welcome-aboard-levante-ud-6/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=welcome-aboard-levante-ud-6</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 12:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Levante]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metrica play]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metrica Play Pro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://metrica-sports.com/?p=1410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are proud to announce that Levante UD, competing in the Spanish League LaLiga, has chosen Metrica Sports for their coaching analysis. Metrica Sports will provide the club with Metrica Play Pro, our new platform powered by artificial intelligence to engage with players efficiently. The agreement will provide coaching staff this desktop platform that allows [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/welcome-aboard-levante-ud-6/">Welcome aboard, Levante UD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are proud to announce that Levante UD, competing in the Spanish  League LaLiga, has chosen Metrica Sports for their coaching analysis. </p>



<p>Metrica Sports will provide the club with <a rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Metrica Play Pro (opens in a new tab)" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/metrica-play-pro/" target="_blank">Metrica Play Pro</a>, our new platform powered by artificial intelligence to engage with players efficiently. </p>



<p>The agreement will provide coaching staff this desktop platform that allows automatic tracking of players for all 22 players in all their games on regular season, not only for their own games analysis, but also for opponent games. This tracking data will provide the team with the ability to look at the game in an unique way: Full match on-video visualizations on their preferred recordings.</p>



<p>We look forward to working closely with Levante UD and support their players and coaches with state-of-the-art automatic tracking technology.</p>


<blockquote>
<p><!--EndFragment--><em data-rich-text-format-boundary="true">Metrica Sports provides a combination of tracking, event and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games.&nbsp; Providing data points 15 times per second, Metrica Play software allows coaches and analysts to make data driven performance decisions and provides a platform to identify technical and tactical movement patterns that are specific to an individual team’s style of play or coaching philosophy. </em></p>
</blockquote> <p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/welcome-aboard-levante-ud-6/">Welcome aboard, Levante UD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vissel Kobe becomes the first Asian team to partner with Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/vissel-kobe-becomes-the-first-asian-team-to-partner-with-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=vissel-kobe-becomes-the-first-asian-team-to-partner-with-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metrica play]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tactical Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vissel Kobe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metricas-cp6.wordpresstemporal.com///?p=5247</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are proud to announce that Vissel Kobe, competing in the Japanese J1 League, has chosen Metrica Sports for their coaching analysis. The club, owned by Rakuten, follows the Group&#8217;s mission to use the best innovations to create value. In quick succession over 18 months the Japanese club reunited Podolski, Iniesta, and Villa, three world-class [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/vissel-kobe-becomes-the-first-asian-team-to-partner-with-metrica-sports/">Vissel Kobe becomes the first Asian team to partner with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are proud to announce that Vissel Kobe, competing in the Japanese J1 League, has chosen Metrica Sports for their coaching analysis. The club, owned by Rakuten, follows the Group&#8217;s mission to use the best innovations to create value.</p>



<p>In quick succession over 18 months the Japanese club reunited Podolski, Iniesta, and Villa, three world-class players who turned Kobe into the center of the Japanese soccer universe and lifted the J. League’s international profile to unprecedented heights. </p>



<p>We look forward to working closely with Vissel Kobe and support their players and coaches with state of the art analysis services. </p>



<p><em>Metrica Sports provides a combination of tracking, event and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games.  Providing data points 15 times per second the Metrica software allows coaches and analysts to make data driven performance decisions and provides a platform to identify technical and tactical movement patterns that are specific to an individual team’s style of play or coaching philosophy.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/vissel-kobe-becomes-the-first-asian-team-to-partner-with-metrica-sports/">Vissel Kobe becomes the first Asian team to partner with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Columbus Crew signs with Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/columbus-crew-signs-with-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=columbus-crew-signs-with-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 14:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metrica Sports are proud to announce a 2 year partnership with founding member of the MLS the Columbus Crew. The addition of Columbus to the growing number of MLS teams using the league’s leading performance analysis and player tracking software Metrica PLAY is an exciting development for Metrica and further highlights the appitite from MLS [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/columbus-crew-signs-with-metrica-sports/">Columbus Crew signs with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Metrica Sports are proud to announce a 2 year partnership with founding member of the MLS the Columbus Crew.</p>



<p>The addition of Columbus to the growing number of MLS teams using the league’s leading performance analysis and player tracking software Metrica PLAY is an exciting development for Metrica and further highlights the appitite from MLS teams for access to data fueled performance insights.</p>



<p>Teams from the MLS accessing the insights provided by Metrica now include, the Professional Referee Organization, Seattle Sounders, LAFC, LA Galaxy, Vancouver Whitecaps, Portland Timbers, Colorado Rapids, Houston Dynamo &amp; Toronto FC in accessing Metrica PLAY.</p>



<p>The partnership with Columbus will provide its coaching staff with access to AI powered tracking data for all 22 players and ball for all regular season and post season MLS games. This tracking data along with event data and Wide-angle autozoom video will allow staff  to look at the game in a custom and unique way via Metrica’s Personal Pattern Alarms which identify and present moments in the game that are related to the Crew’s specific style of play.</p>



<p>Metrica Sports Managing Director, Ewan Robson described how excited Metrica is to have the opportunity to work with the Columbs Crew:</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“We are proud to get the chance to work with President Tim Bezbatchenko and Technical Director Pat Onstad in their efforts to create a data driven approach to player development and performance analysis and have a front row seat in watching the development of this great club under its new ownership.”</p></blockquote>



<p><em>Metrica Sports provides a combination of tracking, event and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games.  Providing data points 15 times per second the Metrica software allows coaches and analysts to make data driven performance decisions and provides a platform to identify technical and tactical movement patterns that are specific to an individual team’s style of play or coaching philosophy.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/columbus-crew-signs-with-metrica-sports/">Columbus Crew signs with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LA Galaxy, Portland Timbers and Vancouver Whitecaps become the latest clubs to join Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/la-galaxy-portland-timbers-and-vancouver-whitecaps-become-the-latest-clubs-to-join-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=la-galaxy-portland-timbers-and-vancouver-whitecaps-become-the-latest-clubs-to-join-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metrica is excited to announce the addition of LA Galaxy, Portland Timbers and the Vancouver Whitecaps as new clients ahead of the 2019 MLS Season. These teams will join current MLS clients, the Professional Referee Organization,&#160; Seattle Sounders, LAFC, Colorado Rapids, Houston Dynamo &#38; Toronto FC in accessing the league’s leading performance analysis and player [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/la-galaxy-portland-timbers-and-vancouver-whitecaps-become-the-latest-clubs-to-join-metrica-sports/">LA Galaxy, Portland Timbers and Vancouver Whitecaps become the latest clubs to join Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Metrica is excited to announce the addition of LA Galaxy,
Portland Timbers and the Vancouver Whitecaps as new clients ahead of the 2019
MLS Season.</p>



<p>These teams will join current MLS clients, the Professional
Referee Organization,&nbsp; Seattle Sounders,
LAFC, Colorado Rapids, Houston Dynamo &amp; Toronto FC in accessing the
league’s leading performance analysis and player tracking software <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RFKQ5pJ3tro">Metrica PLAY</a>. </p>



<p>The agreements will provide coaching staffs with access to AI powered tracking data for all 22 players and ball for all regular season and post season MLS games. This tracking data along with event data and Wide-angle autozoom video will provide teams with the ability to look at the game in a custom and unique way via Metrica’s Personal Pattern Alarms which identify and present moments in the game that are related to each teams specific style of play.</p>



<p>Metrica Sports Managing Director, Ewan Robson described the
significance of adding these new Western Conference teams to the growing number
of clubs in the MLS who have adopted Metrica PLAY&nbsp; </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“We are super excited to get the chance to work with 3 of the most forward-thinking teams in the League to provide them with the ability to look at the game in a more in-depth way from a post-game and scouting perspective. The addition of these teams’ cements Metrica as the leading analysis tool being used within Major League Soccer.”</p></blockquote>



<p><em>Metrica Sports provides a combination of tracking, event and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games.&nbsp; Providing data points 15 times per second the Metrica software allows coaches and analysts to make data driven performance decisions and provides a platform to identify technical and tactical movement patterns that are specific to an individual team’s style of play or coaching philosophy. </em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/la-galaxy-portland-timbers-and-vancouver-whitecaps-become-the-latest-clubs-to-join-metrica-sports/">LA Galaxy, Portland Timbers and Vancouver Whitecaps become the latest clubs to join Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metrica Sports and NVIDIA join forces</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/metrica-sports-and-nvidia-join-forces/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=metrica-sports-and-nvidia-join-forces</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are happy to announce that we have joined the NVIDIA Inception program, which is designed to nurture dedicated and exceptional companies who are revolutionizing industries with advancements in AI and data sciences. The NVIDIA Inception program will help Metrica Sports advanced the field of sports technology through artificial intelligence by proving access to an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/metrica-sports-and-nvidia-join-forces/">Metrica Sports and NVIDIA join forces</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are happy to announce that we have joined the<a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/deep-learning-ai/startups/"> NVIDIA Inception program</a>, which is designed to nurture dedicated and exceptional companies who are revolutionizing industries with advancements in AI and data sciences.</p>



<p>The NVIDIA Inception program will help Metrica
Sports advanced the field of sports technology through artificial intelligence by
proving access to an unmatched combination of knowledge, resources, network and
business development opportunities. </p>



<p>&nbsp;“It’s an honor for us to be a part of the NVIDIA Inception family. Since the early days, we have been at the frontier of innovation in sports technology. &nbsp;Thus, we are always looking for opportunities to join forces with exceptional partners than can help us in our mission of revolutionizing sport technology. This partnership with NVIDIA &nbsp;fits right in and allows us to take full advantage of the new opportunities that AI brings to the table” said Bruno Dagnino, CTO and Co-Founder of Metrica Sports. NVIDIA’s </p>



<p>Inception program is a virtual accelerator program that helps companies during critical stages of product development, prototyping and deployment. Every Inception member gets a custom set of ongoing benefits, from hardware grants and marketing support to training with deep learning experts. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/metrica-sports-and-nvidia-join-forces/">Metrica Sports and NVIDIA join forces</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Physical Module is ON!</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/physical-module-is-on/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=physical-module-is-on</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5044</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest version of Metrica Play has been released, and a new module has been added: You can now decide what data include on your Physical Excel Reports. Stop listing information you don&#8217;t want, start creating your reports in the easiest way: Get a demo now! Be one step ahead. Contact us to start creating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/physical-module-is-on/">Physical Module is ON!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p>The latest version of Metrica Play has been released, and a new module has been added: You can now decide what data include on your Physical Excel Reports. Stop listing information you don&#8217;t want, start creating your reports in the easiest way: </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Physical Module is ON. Customize your own Reports!" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dtjJyLL_A4I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Get a demo now! Be one step ahead. Contact us to start creating your own personalized reports in just a few clicks</p>
 <p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/physical-module-is-on/">Physical Module is ON!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toronto FC signs up for Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/toronto-fc-signs-up-for-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=toronto-fc-signs-up-for-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2017 MLS Champions Toronto FC have signed a partnership with Metrica Sports, joining other MLS and La Liga teams that have adopted the Metrica Sports platform. We provide a combination of tracking data, event data and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games. Providing data points 15times per second the Metrica [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/toronto-fc-signs-up-for-metrica-sports/">Toronto FC signs up for Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>2017 MLS Champions Toronto FC have signed a partnership with Metrica Sports, joining other MLS and La Liga teams that have adopted the Metrica Sports platform.</p>



<p>We provide a combination of tracking data, event data and dynamic video visualizations solutions to track every player’s movement in games. Providing data points 15times per second the Metrica software allows coaches and analysts to make data driven performance decisions and provides a platform to identify technical and tactical movement patterns that are specific to an individual team’s style of play or coaching philosophy.</p>



<p>Currently working with six MLS teams going into the 2018 season, Toronto FC are the most recent club to add contextualized performance analysis to their coaching process.<br> Metrica Managing Director, Ewan Robson, described his excitement at welcoming TFC to the Metrica Sports family.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“We are very proud to be able to provide the current MLS Champions TFC with access to the new era of context driven performance analysis. It is a great opportunity to work with an innovative coaching staff and analytics department to provide a tool to both analyze post game performance along with opponent performance trends.” </p></blockquote>



<p>About TFC<br>
Toronto FC, is a Canadian professional soccer club based in Toronto, Ontario. The club competes is a member of the MLS Eastern Conference playing its home matches at BMO Field.<br>
In 2017 Toronto FC won the domestic treble with the MLS Cup, Supporters’ Shield and Canadian Championship, and set the all-time MLS regular season record for points with 69. They are also six-time winners of the Canadian Championship and were semi-finalists of the 2011–12 CONCACAF Champions League.</p>



<p>To find out what Metrica Sports can do for you, get in touch.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/toronto-fc-signs-up-for-metrica-sports/">Toronto FC signs up for Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LAFC makes a step forward in Performance Analysis, by signing with Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/lafc-makes-a-step-forward-in-performance-analysis-by-signing-with-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=lafc-makes-a-step-forward-in-performance-analysis-by-signing-with-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 21:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to announce an agreement with LAFC for the supply of post-match analysis, and statistical data to assess the performance of their players. The Los Angeles Football Club hired a big-name manager in Bob Bradley, who led the U.S. to a World Cup, and signed big-name players in Mexico’s Carlos Vela, Belgium’s Laurent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/lafc-makes-a-step-forward-in-performance-analysis-by-signing-with-metrica-sports/">LAFC makes a step forward in Performance Analysis, by signing with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are pleased to 
announce an agreement with LAFC for the supply of post-match analysis, 
and statistical data to assess the performance of their players.</p>



<p>The Los Angeles Football Club hired a big-name manager in Bob 
Bradley, who led the U.S. to a World Cup, and signed big-name players in
 Mexico’s Carlos Vela, Belgium’s Laurent Ciman, Costa Rica’s Marcos 
Ureña and Uruguay’s Diego Rossi.</p>



<p>LAFC is Major League Soccer’s 23rd franchise. The club is attracting 
significant attention throughout Los Angeles’ revitalized downtown, 
where it is building the city’s first new open-air stadium in more than 
30 years.</p>



<p>We look forward to working closely with LAFC and support their players and coaches with state of the art analysis services.</p>



<p><strong>To find out what Metrica Sports can do for you, get in touch.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/lafc-makes-a-step-forward-in-performance-analysis-by-signing-with-metrica-sports/">LAFC makes a step forward in Performance Analysis, by signing with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Colorado Rapids signs with Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/colorado-rapids-signs-with-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=colorado-rapids-signs-with-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metrica Sports are delighted to announce Colorado Rapids as the newest club to benefit from our performance analysis solution and services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/colorado-rapids-signs-with-metrica-sports/">Colorado Rapids signs with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Metrica Sports are 
delighted to announce Colorado Rapids as the newest club to benefit from
 our performance analysis solution and services.</p>



<p>The Colorado Rapids open their 23rd MLS season, while ushering in a 
new era for the club with a new coaching staff and an attacking 
philosophy.</p>



<p>We look forward to continuing our support of this game by providing a
 holistic service solution to develop performance on the field.</p>



<p><strong>To find out more about Metrica Sports, get in touch.</strong></p>
 <p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/colorado-rapids-signs-with-metrica-sports/">Colorado Rapids signs with Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valencia CF chooses Metrica Sports</title>
		<link>https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/valencia-cf-chooses-metrica-sports/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=valencia-cf-chooses-metrica-sports</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[metrica_editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 21:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://metrica-sports.com/?p=5154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to give a big welcome to the latest team to join the Metrica Sports family. Valencia CF will benefit from our performance analysis services for the next 3 seasons. Valencia are placed comfortably in the fourth position in the 2017-18&#160;La Liga&#160;with 56 points, one point less than Real Madrid and eight behind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/valencia-cf-chooses-metrica-sports/">Valencia CF chooses Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are pleased to give
 a big welcome to the latest team to join the Metrica Sports family. 
Valencia CF will benefit from our performance analysis services for the 
next 3 seasons.</p>



<p>Valencia are placed comfortably in the fourth position in the 
2017-18&nbsp;La Liga&nbsp;with 56 points, one point less than Real Madrid and 
eight behind second-placed Atletico Madrid. They had finished 12th in 
both the 2015-16 and 2016-17 seasons which saw them change as many as 
six coaches during a difficult phase.</p>



<p>This season, with the arrival of Marcelino García Toral’s staff, 
Valencia CF looks set to earn a place in the UEFA&nbsp;Champions 
League&nbsp;2018-19.</p>



<p>Marcelino and his coaching staff have been working closely with 
Metrica Sports a few years ago, while he was Head Coach of Villarreal 
CF.</p>



<p>“We believe that Metrica Sports will help us by reducing the time we 
spent nowadays in tactical analysis, making it more efficient, and 
empowering the communication with our players through strong facts in a 
visual and intuitive way”, said Marcelino García Toral, Head Coach of 
Valencia CF.</p>



<p>With the objective of making a success out of the challenging next 
season, Valencia CF has decided to contract Metrica Sports to support 
their performance analysis, taking advantage of our advanced tracking 
technology and personalized data analysis tools for both their home and 
away matches.</p>



<p><strong>To find out what Metrica Sports can do for you, get in touch.</strong></p>
 <p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz/valencia-cf-chooses-metrica-sports/">Valencia CF chooses Metrica Sports</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://metrica.preproduccion.xyz">Play</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
